A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.2, Series 300 Latin America - Series 833 Lebanon FA387b
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Japan, 1948-1971; 609; 58 box(es)
  - Japan - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 609.D
    - Tokyo University - Agriculture, 1957-1963 (Box 31, Folder 359)
    - Tokyo University - Aruga, Hisao, 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 360)
    - Tokyo University - Biochemistry, 1957-1959 (Box 31, Folder 361)
    - Tokyo University - Library - Visits, 1961-1962 (Box 31, Folder 362)
    - Tokyo University - Mass Spectrometer, 1957-1962, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 363)
    - Tokyo University - Mine, Itizo, 1959-1961 (Box 31, Folder 364)
    - Tokyo University - Photosynthesis, 1960-1964 (Box 31, Folder 365)
    - Tokyo University - Protein Chemistry, 1958-1959 (Box 32, Folder 366)
    - Tokyo University - Suyehiro, Yasuo, 1957-1958, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 367)
    - Tokyo University - Takahashi, Keiichi, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 368)
    - Tokyo University - Tamura, Saburo, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 369)
    - Tokyo University - Yamamoto, Shutaro, 1960-1961 (Box 32, Folder 370)
    - Tokyo University - Yamasaki, Teruo, 1958-1960 (Box 32, Folder 371)
    - Tokyo University - Yokoyama, Mitsuo, 1961-1962 (Box 32, Folder 372)
    - Tokyo University of Agriculture - Rice Pathology, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 373)
    - Tokyo University of Education - Biochemistry, 1960-1961 (Box 32, Folder 374)
    - Tokyo University of Education - Plant Science, 1957-1961 (Box 32, Folder 375)
    - Tokyo University of Education - Plant Science - Report, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 376)
    - Torii, Kenji, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 377)
    - Yamaguchi University - Agriculture, 1957-1959 (Box 32, Folder 378)
    - Yamaguchi University - Murayama, Jozo Joshua, 1957-1960 (Box 32, Folder 379)
    - Yokohama University - Biochemistry, 1957-1960 (Box 32, Folder 380)
  - Japan - Humanities and Arts, 609.R
    - Aichi University - Chinese Studies - Books, 1951-1955 (Box 33, Folder 381)
    - Aichi University - Chinese Studies - Koiwai, Jun, 1952-1954 (Box 33, Folder 382)
    - American Studies Association - American History, 1949-1954 (Box 33, Folder 383)
    - Ashihara, Yoshinobu, 1954-1955, 1960-1962 (Box 33, Folder 384)
    - Ashihara, Yoshinobu, 1954-1955, 1960-1962 (Box 33, Folder 385)
    - Ashihara, Yoshinobu - Supplemental Material, 1955, 1959-1961 (Box 33, Folder 386)
    - Association for the Study of American Philosophy, 1953-1958 (Box 33, Folder 387)
    - Chu, Saichi, 1956-1957 (Box 33, Folder 388)
    - Doshisha University - Ishimo, Kakuichi, 1957-1958 (Box 33, Folder 389)
    - Education - Kobayashi, Hideya, 1961-1962 (Box 33, Folder 390)
    - Hanazono College of Zen - Contemporary Thought, 1960-1961, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 391)
    - Hanazono College of Zen - Contemporary Thought - Reports, 1960, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 392)
    - Hokkaido University - Slavic Periodicals, 1959-1962 (Box 34, Folder 393)
    - Institute for Research in Language Teaching, Tokyo, 1949-1953 (Box 34, Folder 394)
    - International Christian University - Educational Philosophy, 1953-1961 (Box 34, Folder 395)
    - International Christian University - Educational Philosophy, 1953-1961 (Box 34, Folder 396)
    - International Christian University - Educational Philosophy, 1953-1961 (Box 34, Folder 397)
    - International Christian University - Educational Philosophy, 1953-1961 (Box 34, Folder 398)
    - International Christian University - Student Values, 1959-1966, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 399)
    - International Christian University - Student Values, 1959-1966, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 400)
    - International Christian University - Student Values, 1959-1966, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 401)
    - International Christian University - Student Values, 1959-1966, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 402)
    - International Christian University - Student Values, 1959-1966, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 403)
    - International Christian University - Student Values - Supplemental Material, 1962-1964 (Box 36, Folder 404)
    - International House of Japan - Fukuda, Naomi, 1962-1964 (Box 36, Folder 405)
    - International House of Japan - Gropius, Walter, 1952-1956 (Box 36, Folder 406)
    - International House of Japan - Gropius, Walter - Publications, 1951, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 407)
    - International House of Japan - Library - Reference Book Guide, 1960-1963 (Box 36, Folder 408)
    - International Institute for the Study of Religions in Japan, 1956-1961, 1964-1965 (Box 36, Folder 409)
    - International Institute for the Study of Religions in Japan, 1956-1961, 1964-1965 (Box 36, Folder 410)
    - International Institute for the Study of Religions in Japan - Reports, 1956-1959 (Box 36, Folder 411)
    - Japan Broadcasting Corporation - Nanye, Jiro, 1953-1954 (Box 36, Folder 412)
    - Japan Women's University - Library, 1959-1960 (Box 36, Folder 413)
    - Juntendo University - Genealogy, 1959-1962 (Box 36, Folder 414)
    - Kasai University - Hori, Masato, 1955-1959 (Box 37, Folder 415)
    - Keio University - Library School, 1950-1964, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 416)
    - Keio University - Library School, 1950-1964, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 417)
    - Keio University - Library School, 1950-1964, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 418)
    - Keio University - Library School, 1950-1964, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 419)
    - Keio University - Library School, 1950-1964, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 420)
    - Keio University - Library School, 1950-1964, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 421)
    - Keio University - Library School, 1950-1964, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 422)
    - Keio University - Library School, 1950-1964, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 423)
    - Keio University - Library School - Reports, 1952-1960, 1962-1963 (Box 38, Folder 424)
    - Keio University - Library School - Reports, 1952-1960, 1962-1963 (Box 38, Folder 425)
    - Keio University - Library School - Reports, 1952-1960, 1962-1963 (Box 38, Folder 426)
    - Keio University - Library School - Reports, 1952-1960, 1962-1963 (Box 38, Folder 427)
    - Keio University - Library School - Visits, 1960-1964 (Box 38, Folder 428)
    - Keio University - Philosophy, 1958-1963 (Box 38, Folder 429)
    - Keio University - Philosophy, 1958-1963 (Box 38, Folder 430)
    - Kobe College - Cheek, Mary Asby, 1955-1957 (Box 39, Folder 431)
    - Kobe College - Namba, Monkichi, 1954-1957 (Box 39, Folder 432)
    - Kobe College - Namba, Monkichi, 1954-1957 (Box 39, Folder 433)
    - Kobe College - Namba, Monkichi, 1954-1957 (Box 39, Folder 434)
    - Kokugakuin University - Library, 1955, 1958-1963 (Box 39, Folder 435)
    - Kokugakuin University - Japanese Culture and Classics, 1954-1965 (Box 39, Folder 436)
    - Kokugakuin University - Japanese Culture and Classics, 1954-1965 (Box 39, Folder 437)
    - Kokugakuin University - Japanese Culture and Classics, 1954-1965 (Box 39, Folder 438)
    - Kokugakuin University - Japanese Culture and Classics, 1954-1965 (Box 39, Folder 439)
    - Kokugakuin University - Japanese Culture and Classics - Transactions (KU-JCC), 1957-1959 (Box 40, Folder 440)
    - Kokugakuin University - Japanese Culture and Classics - Transactions (KU-JCC), 1957-1959 (Box 40, Folder 441)
    - Kokugakuin University - Philippi, Donald L., 1958-1961 (Box 40, Folder 442)
    - Kokugakuin University - Werblowsky, R.L.J. Zwi, 1961-1963 (Box 40, Folder 443)
    - Kyoto University - Chinese Literature, 1950-1954 (Box 40, Folder 444)
    - Kyoto University - Hirasawa (Ko) and Kosaka (Masaaki), 1958-1960 (Box 40, Folder 445)
    - Kyoto University - Korean Archaeology, 1952-1957 (Box 40, Folder 446)
    - Kyoto University - Modern Japanese History, 1956-1958 (Box 40, Folder 447)
    - Kyoto University - Modern Japanese History, 1956-1958 (Box 40, Folder 448)
    - Kyoto University - Modern Japanese History, 1959-1962 (Box 41, Folder 449)
    - Kyoto University - Russian Studies, 1957-1958, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 450)
    - Kyoto University - Sato, Koji, 1958-1962 (Box 41, Folder 451)
    - Kyoto University - Takeuchi, Yoshinori, 1960-1962 (Box 41, Folder 452)
    - Kyoto University - Takeuchi, Yoshinori - Report, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 453)
    - Kyushu University - Chinese Thought, 1956-1961, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 454)
    - Kyushu University - Chinese Thought - Publications, 1957-1959 (Box 41, Folder 455)
    - Kyushu University - Chinese Thought - Publications, 1957-1959 (Box 41, Folder 456)
    - Kyushu University - Education - Otake, Masuko, 1954-1955 (Box 41, Folder 457)
    - Kyushu University - Educational Philosophy, 1952-1962 (Box 42, Folder 458)
    - Kyushu University - Educational Philosophy, 1952-1962 (Box 42, Folder 459)
    - Kyushu University - Educational Philosophy, 1952-1962 (Box 42, Folder 460)
    - Kyushu University - Educational Philosophy, 1952-1962 (Box 42, Folder 461)
    - Kyushu University - Educational Philosophy, 1952-1962 (Box 42, Folder 462)
    - Kyushu University - Educational Philosophy, 1952-1962 (Box 42, Folder 463)
    - Kyushu University - Educational Philosophy - Publications, 1957-1958, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 464)
    - Maeda, Yoichi, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 465)
    - Matsuba, Taka, 1957-1958 (Box 42, Folder 466)
    - Musashino Collage of Music - Gagaku Orchestra, 1958-1961 (Box 42, Folder 467)
    - Nagoya University - Comparative Literature, 1951-1956, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 468)
    - Nagoya University - Shimomura, Fujio, 1952-1955 (Box 43, Folder 469)
    - Nakamura, Yukichi, 1958-1959 (Box 43, Folder 470)
    - Nakayama, Shigeru, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 471)
    - National Diet Library, Tokyo - Building Plans, 1954-1956 (Box 43, Folder 472)
    - National Diet Library, Tokyo - Microfilm, 1949-1959 (Box 43, Folder 473)
    - National Diet Library, Tokyo - Microfilm, 1949-1959 (Box 43, Folder 474)
    - National Diet Library, Tokyo - Microfilm, 1949-1959 (Box 43, Folder 475)
    - National Diet Library, Tokyo - Suzuki, Takao, 1961-1962 (Box 43, Folder 476)
    - Nunokawa, Kakuzaemon, 1956-1958 (Box 43, Folder 477)
    - Ochanomizu University - Fujita, Kenji, 1958-1959 (Box 43, Folder 478)
    - Press Personnel, 1948-1949 (Box 43, Folder 479)
    - Press Personnel, 1950-1954 (Box 44, Folder 480)
    - Ryukyu University - Adaniya, Masoyoshi, 1959-1961 (Box 44, Folder 481)
    - Ryukyu University - Ceramics, 1961-1963 (Box 44, Folder 482)
    - Ryukyu University - Chinese Studies, 1955-1959 (Box 44, Folder 483)
    - Ryukyu University - Fletcher, Charlie May (Mrs. John Gould Fletcher), 1957-1958 (Box 44, Folder 484)
    - Ryukyu University - Goeku, Chosho, 1955-1956 (Box 44, Folder 485)
    - Ryukyu University - History, 1951-1952 (Box 44, Folder 486)
    - Ryukyu University - Library Development, 1957-1964 (Box 44, Folder 487)
    - Ryukyu University - Library Material, 1953-1959 (Box 44, Folder 488)
    - Ryukyu University - Visits, 1957-1959, 1961 (Box 44, Folder 489)
    - Saito, Soichi, 1955-1959 (Box 44, Folder 490)
    - Science Council of Japan - Religious History Conference, 1956-1959 (Box 45, Folder 491)
    - Tohoku University - Ishizu, Teruji, 1960-1961 (Box 45, Folder 492)
    - Tokyo Institute of Technology - Seike, Kiyosi, 1955-1956 (Box 45, Folder 493)
    - Tokyo Metropolitan Hibiya Library - Tanaka, Hikoyasu, 1959 (Box 45, Folder 494)
    - Tokyo Union Theological Seminary - Miyamoto, Takenosuke, 1954-1955 (Box 45, Folder 495)
    - Tokyo Union Theological Seminary - Philosophy, 1958-1961 (Box 45, Folder 496)
    - Tokyo University - Hayashi, Kentaro, 1959-1961, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 497)
    - Tokyo University - Kishimoto, Hideo, 1950-1960 (Box 45, Folder 498)
    - Tokyo University - Language and Thought, 1950-1954 (Box 45, Folder 499)
    - Tokyo University - Language and Thought, 1950-1954 (Box 45, Folder 500)
    - Tokyo University - Librarianship, 1948-1950 (Box 45, Folder 501)
    - Tokyo University - Library, 1957-1966 (Box 46, Folder 502)
    - Tokyo University - Library, 1957-1966 (Box 46, Folder 503)
    - Tokyo University - Library, 1957-1966 (Box 46, Folder 504)
    - Tokyo University - Library, 1957-1966 (Box 46, Folder 505)
    - Tokyo University - Library, 1957-1966 (Box 46, Folder 506)
    - Tokyo University - Library, 1957-1966 (Box 46, Folder 507)
    - Tokyo University - Library - Reports, 1961-1964 (Box 46, Folder 508)
    - Tokyo University - Library - Reports, 1961-1964 (Box 46, Folder 509)
    - Tokyo University - Library - Visits, 1960-1961 (Box 46, Folder 510)
    - Tokyo University - Political Biographies, 1953-1958, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 511)
    - Tokyo University - Press - Minowa, Shigeo, 1959-1962 (Box 47, Folder 512)
    - Tokyo University - Ueda, Tsutomu, 1956-1958 (Box 47, Folder 513)
    - Tokyo University - Yamamoto, Tatsuro, 1960-1961 (Box 47, Folder 514)
    - Tokyo University of Arts - Western Musicology, 1956-1959 (Box 47, Folder 515)
    - Tokyo University of Foreign Studies - Masutani, Fumio, 1960-1962 (Box 47, Folder 516)
    - Toyo Bunko - Chinese History, 1953-1960 (Box 47, Folder 517)
    - Toyo Bunko - Chinese History, 1953-1960 (Box 47, Folder 518)
    - Toyo Bunko - Chinese History, 1953-1960 (Box 47, Folder 519)
    - Toyo Bunko - Chinese History, 1953-1960 (Box 47, Folder 520)
    - Toyo Bunko - Tibetan Studies, 1959-1964 (Box 47, Folder 521)
    - Wakayama University - Inoue, Soji, 1954-1958 (Box 48, Folder 522)
    - Waseda University - Drama Lectures, 1952-1957 (Box 48, Folder 523)
    - Waseda University - Nishijima, Shigetada, 1955-1963 (Box 48, Folder 524)
    - Waseda University - Nishijima, Shigetada, 1955-1963 (Box 48, Folder 525)
    - Waseda University - Nishijima, Shigetada, 1955-1963 (Box 48, Folder 526)
    - Waseda University - Tatsunokuchi, Naotaro, 1954, 1956-1959 (Box 48, Folder 527)
    - Waseda University - Uyeda, Seizi, 1958-1959 (Box 48, Folder 528)
  - Japan - Social Sciences, 609.S
    - Doshisha University - Bronfenbrenner, Martin, 1951-1952 (Box 48, Folder 529)
    - Economic Planning Agency - Ohkawa, Kazushi, 1957-1960 (Box 48, Folder 530)
    - Economic Planning Agency - Okita, Saburo, 1954, 1956-1959 (Box 48, Folder 531)
    - Hata, Ikuhiko, 1962-1965, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 532)
    - Hiroshima University - Horikawa, Takeo, 1955-1956 (Box 49, Folder 533)
    - Hiroshima University - Horikawa, Takeo - Reports, 1955-1956 (Box 49, Folder 534)
    - Hiroshima University - Horikawa, Takeo - Reports, 1955-1956 (Box 49, Folder 535)
    - Hiroshima University - Kotani, Tsuruji, 1956-1959 (Box 49, Folder 536)
    - Hiroshima University - Social Sciences, 1956-1961 (Box 49, Folder 537)
    - Hitotsubashi University - Economic Research, 1954, 1956-1963, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 538)
    - Hitotsubashi University - Hosoya, Chihiro, 1960-1963 (Box 50, Folder 539)
    - Hitotsubashi University - Itagaki, Yoichi, 1956-1958 (Box 50, Folder 540)
    - Hokkaido University - Agricultural Economics, 1948-1952 (Box 50, Folder 541)
    - Institute of Statistical Mathematics - Matusita, Kameo, 1956-1959 (Box 50, Folder 542)
    - International House of Japan - Japanese-American Relations, 1960-1964 (Box 50, Folder 543)
    - International Organization and Relations, 1951-1953 (Box 50, Folder 544)
    - Japan Institute of Pacific Studies - Yanaihara, Tadeo, 1950 (Box 50, Folder 545)
    - Japan Political Science Association - Nambara, Shigeru, 1952 (Box 50, Folder 546)
    - Japan Public Administration Clearing House, 1950-1954 (Box 51, Folder 547)
    - Japan Public Administration Clearing House, 1950-1954 (Box 51, Folder 548)
    - Japan Sociological Society - Social Stratification, 1953-1958 (Box 51, Folder 549)
    - Japanese Association of International Law, 1954-1956 (Box 51, Folder 550)
    - Japanese Communism Study, 1950-1953 (Box 51, Folder 551)
    - Kagawa University - Kodama, Yoichi, 1960-1961 (Box 51, Folder 552)
    - Keio University - Japanese Fishing Village Studies, 1952, 1954-1957, 1959 (Box 51, Folder 553)
    - Keio University - Japanese Fishing Village Studies - Report, 1958 (Box 51, Folder 554)
    - Keio University - Social Sciences, 1948-1950, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 555)
    - Kobe University - Tanaka, Kinji, 1955-1956 (Box 52, Folder 556)
    - Kyoto University - Economics, 1952-1954, 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 557)
    - Kyoto University - Inoki, Masamichi, 1960-1966 (Box 52, Folder 558)
    - Kyoto University - Inoki, Masamichi, 1960-1966 (Box 52, Folder 559)
    - Kyoto University - Japanese Values Study, 1952, 1954-1963 (Box 52, Folder 560)
    - Kyoto University - Japanese Values Study, 1952, 1954-1963 (Box 52, Folder 561)
    - Kyoto University - Katsuda, Kichitaro, 1961-1964 (Box 52, Folder 562)
    - Kyoto University - Kometani, Eiji, 1957-1959 (Box 52, Folder 563)
    - Kyoto University - Kosaka, Masataka, 1963-1965 (Box 52, Folder 564)
    - Kyoto University - Law Library, 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 565)
    - Kyoto University - United Nations Depository Library, 1960-1962 (Box 53, Folder 566)
    - Kyushu University - Books, 1956-1959 (Box 53, Folder 567)
    - Kyushu University - Mathematical Statistics, 1956-1959 (Box 53, Folder 568)
    - Kyushu University - Mathematical Statistics - Kitagawa, Tosio, 1956-1958 (Box 53, Folder 569)
    - Nagoya University - Kitagawa, Kazuo, 1956-1957 (Box 53, Folder 570)
    - Nagoya University - Social Sciences, 1956-1958 (Box 53, Folder 571)
    - National Defense College - Kotani, Hidejiro, 1960-1961 (Box 53, Folder 572)
    - National Diet Library, Tokyo, 1948-1955 (Box 53, Folder 573)
    - National Diet Library, Tokyo, 1948-1955 (Box 53, Folder 574)
    - National Diet Library, Tokyo, 1948-1955 (Box 53, Folder 575)
    - National Diet Library, Tokyo - Catalog, 1952 (Box 53, Folder 576)
    - Osaka University - Econometrics, 1960-1964 (Box 54, Folder 577)
    - Osaka University - Economics, 1953-1962, 1964-1965 (Box 54, Folder 578)
    - Osaka University - Economics, 1953-1962, 1964-1965 (Box 54, Folder 579)
    - Osaka University - Economics, 1953-1962, 1964-1965 (Box 54, Folder 580)
    - Osaka University - Economics, 1953-1962, 1964-1965 (Box 54, Folder 581)
    - Osaka University - Economics - Publications, 1953-1961 (Box 54, Folder 582)
    - Osaka University - Economics - Publications, 1953-1961 (Box 54, Folder 583)
    - Osaka University - Economics - Symposium, 1959 (Box 54, Folder 584)
    - Osaka University - Ichimura, Shinichi, 1954-1956 (Box 55, Folder 585)
    - Research Institute of Population Problems, 1951-1956 (Box 55, Folder 586)
    - Research Institute of Population Problems - Books, 1952-1955 (Box 55, Folder 587)
    - Research Institute of Population Problems - Okasaki, Ayanori, 1953 (Box 55, Folder 588)
    - Sophia University - Munakata, Peter F., 1956-1959 (Box 55, Folder 589)
    - Supreme Court Library, 1954-1957, 1960-1961 (Box 55, Folder 590)
    - Tohoku University - Library, 1959-1960 (Box 55, Folder 591)
    - Tohoku University - Yasui, Takuma, 1959-1961 (Box 55, Folder 592)
    - Tokyo Institute for Municipal Research - Kojima, Reikichi, 1953-1956, 1958, 1960 (Box 55, Folder 593)
    - Tokyo Institute for Municipal Research - Library, 1946-1951 (Box 55, Folder 594)
    - Tokyo Metropolitan University - Ogura, Kuraji, 1956-1958 (Box 56, Folder 595)
    - Tokyo University - Fukuda, Kan-ichi, 1957-1958 (Box 56, Folder 596)
    - Tokyo University - International Relations, 1959-1968 (Box 56, Folder 597)
    - Tokyo University - International Relations, 1959-1968 (Box 56, Folder 598)
    - Tokyo University - International Relations, 1959-1968 (Box 56, Folder 599)
    - Tokyo University - International Relations, 1959-1968 (Box 56, Folder 600)
    - Tokyo University - Maruyama, Masao, 1961-1963 (Box 56, Folder 601)
    - Tokyo University of Commerce, 1949-1950, 1953 (Box 56, Folder 602)
    - Wakayama University - Matsumura, Zentaro, 1959-1961, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 603)
    - Waseda University - Hayashi, Yokichi, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 604)
    - Waseda University - Highway Transportation, 1956-1960, 1963-1964 (Box 56, Folder 605)
    - Waseda University - Kashiwazaki, Toshinosuke, 1956-1958 (Box 56, Folder 606)
    - Waseda University - Katsumura, Shigeru, 1960-1962 (Box 56, Folder 607)
  - Japan - Virus Studies, 609.V
    - Kyoto University, 1958-1964 (Box 57, Folder 608)
    - Kyushu University, 1956-1958, 1960-1961, 1963-1964 (Box 57, Folder 609)
    - National Institute of Health, 1956-1963 (Box 57, Folder 610)
    - National Institute of Health, 1956-1963 (Box 57, Folder 611)
    - National Institute of Health, 1956-1963 (Box 57, Folder 612)
    - National Institute of Health, 1956-1963 (Box 57, Folder 613)
    - National Institute of Health, 1956-1963 (Box 57, Folder 614)
    - National Institute of Health, 1964-1968 (Box 58, Folder 615)
    - National Institute of Health, 1964-1968 (Box 58, Folder 616)
    - National Institute of Health - Annual Reports, 1959-1961 (Box 58, Folder 617)
    - National Institute of Health - Kono, Reisaku, 1964 (Box 58, Folder 618)
    - National Institute of Health - Supplementary Material, 1957-1958 (Box 58, Folder 619)
    - National Institute of Health - Tagaya, Isamu, 1957-1959 (Box 58, Folder 620)
    - Tohoku University, 1961-1962 (Box 58, Folder 621)
    - Tohoku University - Kuroya, Masahiko, 1956-1958 (Box 58, Folder 622)
    - Tokyo Institute of Public Health, 1954-1957, 1959 (Box 58, Folder 623)
    - Tokyo University, 1959-1961 (Box 58, Folder 624)
    - Tokyo University - Matumoto, Minoru, 1962 (Box 58, Folder 625)
    - Yokohama City University, 1960-1964, 1967 (Box 58, Folder 626)
- Korea, 1947-1972; 613; 4 box(es)
  Six subseries as follows: 613 A Medical sciences (research conducted in medical schools or medical research institutes, research directly applicable to the mental and physical health of human beings) 613 C Nursing (nursing education, public health nursing) 613 D Natural sciences and agriculture (research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture) 613 E Fellowships, scholarships, training awards 613 R Humanities and arts 613 S Social sciences
  - Korea - Medical Sciences, 613.A
    - Medical Literature Aid, 1954-1956 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - National Institute for Prevention of Infectious Deseases - Literature Aid, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Seoul National University - Preventative Medicine - Shim, Sang Whang, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Korea - Nursing, 613.C
    - National Postgraduate School of Nursing, Seoul, 1955-1958 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Korea - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 613.D
    - Seoul National University - Forestry, 1958-1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Korea - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 613.E
    - Kim, Duk-Bok, 1968-1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Korea - Humanities and Arts, 613.R
    - Art Society of Korea, 1954-1959 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Chin-Tan Society - Korean History, 1954-1956, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Chun, Pilsoon L., 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Dong Kook University - Comparative Literature - Books, 1961-1964, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Koh, Byongik, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Korea University - Asiatic Research Center, 1958-1962 (Box 1, Folder 12-13)
    - Korea University - Zo, Kiz-Jun, 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Korean Language Society - Korean Dictionary, 1947-1959 (Box 2, Folder 15-18)
    - Korean Research Institute for Dramatic Arts, Inc., 1958-1961 (Box 2, Folder 19-22)
    - Lim, Won-Sik, 1948, 1957-1960 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - National Museums of Korea, 1948-1956 (Box 3, Folder 24-27)
    - National Museums of Korea - Kim, Won Yong, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Seoul National University - Arts, 1958-1960, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Seoul National University - Kim, Sei Hyung, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Seoul National University - Kim, Won-Yong, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Seoul National University - Lee, Hye-Ku, 1958-1962 (Box 3, Folder 32-33)
    - Seoul National University - Yi, Pyeng, Do, 1956-1959 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Sal, Kuk Whan, 1956-1958, 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 35)